<Type Name="TimeWindow" FullName="Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow">
  <TypeSignature Language="C#" Value="public class TimeWindow" />
  <TypeSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".class public auto ansi beforefieldinit TimeWindow extends System.Object" />
  <TypeSignature Language="DocId" Value="T:Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow" />
  <TypeSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Class TimeWindow" />
  <TypeSignature Language="F#" Value="type TimeWindow = class" />
  <AssemblyInfo>
    <AssemblyName>Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor</AssemblyName>
    <AssemblyVersion>0.25.2.0</AssemblyVersion>
    <AssemblyVersion>0.25.4.0</AssemblyVersion>
    <AssemblyVersion>0.26.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
    <AssemblyVersion>0.27.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
    <AssemblyVersion>0.28.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
  </AssemblyInfo>
  <Base>
    <BaseTypeName>System.Object</BaseTypeName>
  </Base>
  <Interfaces />
  <Docs>
    <summary>
            A specific date-time for the profile.
            </summary>
    <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
  </Docs>
  <Members>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public TimeWindow ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.#ctor" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New ()" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>0.28.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
            Initializes a new instance of the TimeWindow class.
            </summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public TimeWindow (DateTime start, DateTime end, string timeZone = default);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor(valuetype System.DateTime start, valuetype System.DateTime end, string timeZone) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.#ctor(System.DateTime,System.DateTime,System.String)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New (start As DateTime, end As DateTime, Optional timeZone As String = Nothing)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="new Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow : DateTime * DateTime * string -&gt; Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow" Usage="new Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow (start, end, timeZone)" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>0.28.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="start" Type="System.DateTime" />
        <Parameter Name="end" Type="System.DateTime" />
        <Parameter Name="timeZone" Type="System.String" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="start">the start time for the profile in ISO 8601
            format.</param>
        <param name="end">the end time for the profile in ISO 8601
            format.</param>
        <param name="timeZone">the timezone of the start and end times for
            the profile. Some examples of valid time zones are: Dateline
            Standard Time, UTC-11, Hawaiian Standard Time, Alaskan Standard
            Time, Pacific Standard Time (Mexico), Pacific Standard Time, US
            Mountain Standard Time, Mountain Standard Time (Mexico), Mountain
            Standard Time, Central America Standard Time, Central Standard
            Time, Central Standard Time (Mexico), Canada Central Standard Time,
            SA Pacific Standard Time, Eastern Standard Time, US Eastern
            Standard Time, Venezuela Standard Time, Paraguay Standard Time,
            Atlantic Standard Time, Central Brazilian Standard Time, SA Western
            Standard Time, Pacific SA Standard Time, Newfoundland Standard
            Time, E. South America Standard Time, Argentina Standard Time, SA
            Eastern Standard Time, Greenland Standard Time, Montevideo Standard
            Time, Bahia Standard Time, UTC-02, Mid-Atlantic Standard Time,
            Azores Standard Time, Cape Verde Standard Time, Morocco Standard
            Time, UTC, GMT Standard Time, Greenwich Standard Time, W. Europe
            Standard Time, Central Europe Standard Time, Romance Standard Time,
            Central European Standard Time, W. Central Africa Standard Time,
            Namibia Standard Time, Jordan Standard Time, GTB Standard Time,
            Middle East Standard Time, Egypt Standard Time, Syria Standard
            Time, E. Europe Standard Time, South Africa Standard Time, FLE
            Standard Time, Turkey Standard Time, Israel Standard Time,
            Kaliningrad Standard Time, Libya Standard Time, Arabic Standard
            Time, Arab Standard Time, Belarus Standard Time, Russian Standard
            Time, E. Africa Standard Time, Iran Standard Time, Arabian Standard
            Time, Azerbaijan Standard Time, Russia Time Zone 3, Mauritius
            Standard Time, Georgian Standard Time, Caucasus Standard Time,
            Afghanistan Standard Time, West Asia Standard Time, Ekaterinburg
            Standard Time, Pakistan Standard Time, India Standard Time, Sri
            Lanka Standard Time, Nepal Standard Time, Central Asia Standard
            Time, Bangladesh Standard Time, N. Central Asia Standard Time,
            Myanmar Standard Time, SE Asia Standard Time, North Asia Standard
            Time, China Standard Time, North Asia East Standard Time, Singapore
            Standard Time, W. Australia Standard Time, Taipei Standard Time,
            Ulaanbaatar Standard Time, Tokyo Standard Time, Korea Standard
            Time, Yakutsk Standard Time, Cen. Australia Standard Time, AUS
            Central Standard Time, E. Australia Standard Time, AUS Eastern
            Standard Time, West Pacific Standard Time, Tasmania Standard Time,
            Magadan Standard Time, Vladivostok Standard Time, Russia Time Zone
            10, Central Pacific Standard Time, Russia Time Zone 11, New Zealand
            Standard Time, UTC+12, Fiji Standard Time, Kamchatka Standard Time,
            Tonga Standard Time, Samoa Standard Time, Line Islands Standard
            Time</param>
        <summary>
            Initializes a new instance of the TimeWindow class.
            </summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="End">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public DateTime End { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance valuetype System.DateTime End" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.End" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property End As DateTime" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.End : DateTime with get, set" Usage="Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.End" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>0.28.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName Language="C#">[Newtonsoft.Json.JsonProperty(PropertyName="end")]</AttributeName>
          <AttributeName Language="F#">[&lt;Newtonsoft.Json.JsonProperty(PropertyName="end")&gt;]</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.DateTime</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
            Gets or sets the end time for the profile in ISO 8601 format.
            </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Start">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public DateTime Start { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance valuetype System.DateTime Start" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.Start" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property Start As DateTime" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.Start : DateTime with get, set" Usage="Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.Start" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>0.28.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName Language="C#">[Newtonsoft.Json.JsonProperty(PropertyName="start")]</AttributeName>
          <AttributeName Language="F#">[&lt;Newtonsoft.Json.JsonProperty(PropertyName="start")&gt;]</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.DateTime</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
            Gets or sets the start time for the profile in ISO 8601 format.
            </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="TimeZone">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string TimeZone { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string TimeZone" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.TimeZone" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property TimeZone As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="member this.TimeZone : string with get, set" Usage="Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.TimeZone" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>0.28.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName Language="C#">[Newtonsoft.Json.JsonProperty(PropertyName="timeZone")]</AttributeName>
          <AttributeName Language="F#">[&lt;Newtonsoft.Json.JsonProperty(PropertyName="timeZone")&gt;]</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
            Gets or sets the timezone of the start and end times for the
            profile. Some examples of valid time zones are: Dateline Standard
            Time, UTC-11, Hawaiian Standard Time, Alaskan Standard Time,
            Pacific Standard Time (Mexico), Pacific Standard Time, US Mountain
            Standard Time, Mountain Standard Time (Mexico), Mountain Standard
            Time, Central America Standard Time, Central Standard Time, Central
            Standard Time (Mexico), Canada Central Standard Time, SA Pacific
            Standard Time, Eastern Standard Time, US Eastern Standard Time,
            Venezuela Standard Time, Paraguay Standard Time, Atlantic Standard
            Time, Central Brazilian Standard Time, SA Western Standard Time,
            Pacific SA Standard Time, Newfoundland Standard Time, E. South
            America Standard Time, Argentina Standard Time, SA Eastern Standard
            Time, Greenland Standard Time, Montevideo Standard Time, Bahia
            Standard Time, UTC-02, Mid-Atlantic Standard Time, Azores Standard
            Time, Cape Verde Standard Time, Morocco Standard Time, UTC, GMT
            Standard Time, Greenwich Standard Time, W. Europe Standard Time,
            Central Europe Standard Time, Romance Standard Time, Central
            European Standard Time, W. Central Africa Standard Time, Namibia
            Standard Time, Jordan Standard Time, GTB Standard Time, Middle East
            Standard Time, Egypt Standard Time, Syria Standard Time, E. Europe
            Standard Time, South Africa Standard Time, FLE Standard Time,
            Turkey Standard Time, Israel Standard Time, Kaliningrad Standard
            Time, Libya Standard Time, Arabic Standard Time, Arab Standard
            Time, Belarus Standard Time, Russian Standard Time, E. Africa
            Standard Time, Iran Standard Time, Arabian Standard Time,
            Azerbaijan Standard Time, Russia Time Zone 3, Mauritius Standard
            Time, Georgian Standard Time, Caucasus Standard Time, Afghanistan
            Standard Time, West Asia Standard Time, Ekaterinburg Standard Time,
            Pakistan Standard Time, India Standard Time, Sri Lanka Standard
            Time, Nepal Standard Time, Central Asia Standard Time, Bangladesh
            Standard Time, N. Central Asia Standard Time, Myanmar Standard
            Time, SE Asia Standard Time, North Asia Standard Time, China
            Standard Time, North Asia East Standard Time, Singapore Standard
            Time, W. Australia Standard Time, Taipei Standard Time, Ulaanbaatar
            Standard Time, Tokyo Standard Time, Korea Standard Time, Yakutsk
            Standard Time, Cen. Australia Standard Time, AUS Central Standard
            Time, E. Australia Standard Time, AUS Eastern Standard Time, West
            Pacific Standard Time, Tasmania Standard Time, Magadan Standard
            Time, Vladivostok Standard Time, Russia Time Zone 10, Central
            Pacific Standard Time, Russia Time Zone 11, New Zealand Standard
            Time, UTC+12, Fiji Standard Time, Kamchatka Standard Time, Tonga
            Standard Time, Samoa Standard Time, Line Islands Standard Time
            </summary>
        <value>To be added.</value>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Validate">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public virtual void Validate ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig newslot virtual instance void Validate() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor.Models.TimeWindow.Validate" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overridable Sub Validate ()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="F#" Value="abstract member Validate : unit -&gt; unit&#xA;override this.Validate : unit -&gt; unit" Usage="timeWindow.Validate " />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>Microsoft.Azure.Management.Monitor</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>0.28.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
            Validate the object.
            </summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
        <exception cref="T:Microsoft.Rest.ValidationException">
            Thrown if validation fails
            </exception>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
  </Members>
</Type>
